Finding your inner princess can be such a royal pain.
The Prince & Me is a comedy, romance film directed by Martha Coolidge.
A fairy tale love-story about pre-med student Paige who falls in love with a Danish Prince "Eddie" who refused to
follow the traditions of his parents and has come to the US to quench his thirst for rebellion.
Paige and Edward come from two different worlds, but there
is an undeniable attraction between them.
Paige Morgan, played by Julia Stiles.
Prince Edvard, played by Luke Mably.
Soren, played by Ben Miller.
Queen Rosalind, played by Miranda Richardson.
King Haraald, played by James Fox.
Amy Morgan, played by Alberta Watson.
The Prince & Me is a 2004 American romantic comedy film directed by Martha Coolidge, and starring Julia
Stiles, Luke Mably and Ben Miller, with Miranda Richardson, James Fox and Alberta Watson.
The film focuses on Paige Morgan, a pre-med college student in Wisconsin, who is
pursued by a Danish prince posing as an ordinary college student.
The film had 3 direct-to-video sequels created under different writers and a new director, with Kam Heskin replacing Julia Stiles in the role of Paige Morgan:
The Prince & Me 2: The Royal Wedding (2006), The Prince & Me: A Royal Honeymoon (2008), and The Prince & Me: The Elephant Adventure (2010).
The film explores themes of secret identity, wisconsin, prince, college, romcom.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.